<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Poker: 24 Points</string>
    <string name="btn_refresh">Rafraîchir</string>
    <string name="btn_findSolution">Encontrer une solution</string>
    <string name="btn_validate">Confirmer</string>
    <string name="eTxt_solution">Ecrire votre solution</string>
    <string name="you_lost">Vous avez perdu!!!</string>
    <string name="you_won">Vous avez gagné!!!</string>
    <string name="no_solution">No hay solution!</string>
    <string name="time_remain">Temp resté: </string>
    <string name="card_remain">Carte restée: </string>
    <string name="form_invalid">Formule non invalide</string>
    <string name="card_invalid">Numero carte non invalide</string>
    <string name="op_invalid">Operation non invalide</string>
    <string name="rules">Règles</string>
    <string name="recommend">Recommander</string>
    <string name="landscape">landscape</string>
    <string name="portrait">portrait</string>
    <string name="timer_up">Timer\'s up</string>
    <string name="scores">Scores: </string>
    <string name="about">Au sujet de</string>

    <string name="howTo">How to play:</string>
    <string name="rule1">Each number card represent the value as the card number, Jack, Queen and King represent the values 11, 12, and 13, respectively. </string>
    <string name="rule2">The objective is to find a way to manipulate four numbers(integers) so that the end result is 24.</string>
    <string name="rule3">If your solution results 24, you score 4 points. If you do not get your solution within one minute, you lose 4 points </string>
    <string name="rule4">If you do not know the solution, press FIND A SOLUTION: if there is no solution, you score 2 points, but if there is a solution, if you lose 4 points.</string>
    <string name="rule5">If you do not provide any solution, you lose 4 points.</string>

    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="sendMsg">Checkout this cool App follow this link. http://www.richyan.com/android/poke24points</string>
    <string name="share">Partager avec</string>

    <string name="aboutGame">About the Game:</string>
    <string name="about1">The game has been played in Shanghai since the 1960s, using playing cards. It is similar to the card game Maths24.</string>
    <string name="about2">The original version of 24 is played with an ordinary deck of playing cards with all the face cards removed.
        The aces are taken to have the value 1 and the basic game proceeds by having 4 cards dealt and the first player that can achieve the number 24 exactly using only allowed operations
        (addition, subtraction, multiplication, division, and parentheses) wins the hand. Some advanced players allow exponentiation, roots, logarithms, and other operations.</string>
    <string name="about3">Mental arithmetic and fast thinking are necessary skills for competitive play. Pencil and paper will slow down a player, and are generally not allowed during play anyway.</string>
    <string name="designedBy">Designed By: Rich Yan</string>
</resources>
